(Sheldon:)I'm all but certain there's a Nobel Prize
in my future.
(Sheldon:)Actually, I shouldn't say that.
I'm entirely certain.
(Sheldon:)No, Mother, I could not feel
your church group praying for my safety.
(Sheldon:)The fact that I'm home safe
doesn't prove it worked.
(Sheldon:)That logic is post hoc
ergo propter hoc.
(Sheldon:)No, I'm not sassing you
in Eskimo talk.
-I'm gonna let Penny know we're back.
-Mother, I have to go.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, love you. Bye.
(Sheldon:)Hello, old friend.
[SIGHS]
(Sheldon:)Daddy's home.
(Penny:)Leonard, you're back.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I just stopped by to say--
(Leonard:)-Yeah, so hi.
-Hi.
Damn it, I should've gone over
and told her we were back.
(Raj:)Yeah, it was first come, first serve.